Aaron Davis

Gold Bar, WA

425-366-9028

famousmusicinc@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaron-davis-60b643139

Revenue-driven successful sales manager with expertise in telecommunications and technology. Additionally, comprehensive problem solver specializing in management, company growth, competitive sales, and marketing.

Objective

My goal is to find a company that can utilize my sales experience, hopefully somewhere closer to home and closer to a 9am to 5pm schedule. The majority of my experience is in the telecommunications industry so employers with a focus in that field are a huge plus. In short, I need a career that will better enable me to have my personal life as well as my work life.

Skills

Microsoft Office (6 years), Machine Operation (1 year), Computer Literacy (8 years), Online Marketing (1 year), Merchandising (2 years), Sales Management (2 years), Assembly, Cooking (2 years), Painting (1 year), Office Administration (1 year), Customer Service (4 years), Online Marketing (4 years), Ecommerce (1 year), Marketing (2 years), Online Marketing (2 years), Social Media Marketing (2 years)

Work History

Sales Management

Car Toys - Burlington, WA September 2016 to Present

Providing expert product selection advice so that customers purchase products that meet their individual needs and wishes. Meeting or exceeding all CSE customer service and performance minimum standards. Actively establishing working relationships based on trust and mutual respect. Demonstrating the Company Guiding Principles in all interactions with Company customers and other employees.

Store Manager

Cricket Wireless Authorized Retailer - Everett, WA

December 2015 to September 2016

Responsibilities include, Managing team of four to five employees, accountability for stores performance and sales metrics, training sales team in best business practices, organizing community events to drive traffic and business exposure.

Sales Associate

Best Buy - Marysville, WA March 2015 to December 2015 Retail sales associate for Best Buy Mobil

E-Commerce Manager

Big Box Outlet - Monroe, WA February 2014 to March 2015

Responsibilities include, Managing all aspects of our online sales division. Photographing merchandise, Communication with customers, Multi tasking, Managing many simultaneous customer orders, etc.

Assistant Manager

Gamestop - Everett, WA July 2013 to February 2015

Aaron Davis

Gold Bar, WA

425-366-9028

famousmusicinc@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaron-davis-60b643139

Work History Continued

Technical Support Representative

Xerox Corporation - Redmond, WA September 2012 to February 2014

Operated phone support line and delivered technical assistance to Google Play (android) customers.

Swiss Lathe Operator

Advantage Manufacturing Technologies - Monroe, WA

April 2012 to May 2013

Machinist Level II Trained in Daily use of precision measuring equipment and in slandered operation and upkeep of Swiss Lathes.

Assembly Line Worker

Boeing/Workforce - Mukilteo, WA September 2007 to May 2008

Training in Assembly, Rivet, Quality Assurance, Small parts and Kiting, Paint and Finish.

Education

Associates in Computer Information Systems

Everett Community College - Everett, WA 2015 to 2018

GED in General

Sultan High school - Sultan, WA 2008

References

References available apon request